Guide to Peter P. Carr Papers RG.055
Poly Archives at the Bern Dibner Library of Science and Technology, NYU Libraries
- Series IV: Binomial Local Time (BLT), 1988-1991
  - Binomial Model of Eur. Option Valuation with Exg Fwd Price, Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Draft EOV, 1989; 60 Linear Feet (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Carr & Jarrow, The Stop-Loss Start-Gain Paradox and Option Valuation, 1988; 60 Linear Feet (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Allowing Drift, 1988; 60 Linear Feet (Box 5, Folder 26)
- Series V: Bonds with Detachable Warrants & Cox-Ingersall-Ross (CIR), 1973-2000
  - Omberg, Edward; On the Theory of Perfect Heding, 1987-1988; 60 Linear Feet (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Omberg, Ed; Binary Trading Strategies, Brownian Local Time and the Tanaka Formulas, 1988; 60 Linear Feet (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - Options Bibliography, Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - Exotics Bibliography, 1995-07-01; 60 Linear Feet (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - Lookback Options Bibliography, Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - Stochastic Volatility Bibliography, Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - Brealey & Pyle, A Bibliography of Finance and Investment, 1973; 60 Linear Feet (Box 5, Item 1)
  - Valuing Bonds with Detachable Warrants, Peter Carr, 1991; 60 Linear Feet (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - Popular Press, 1989-1990; 60 Linear Feet (Box 5, Folder 34)
  - Valuing Bonds with Detachable Warrants; Carr, Peter (2), Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - Comments on "Valuing Bonds with Detachable Warrants", 1990; 60 Linear Feet (Box 5, Folder 36)
  - Japanese Equity Warrant Publications, 1988-1990 (Box 5, Folder 37)
  - Valuing Bonds w/ Detachable Warrants Manuscript & Floppy Disk, Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 5, Folder 38)
  - Japanese Financial Market Research, 1990-11; 60 Linear Feet (Box 5, Folder 39)
  - Conferences, 1990; 60 Linear Feet (Box 5, Folder 40)
  - Warrants Traded in UK, 1989; 60 Linear Feet (Box 5, Folder 41)
  - Peter Carr Bonds Floppy Disk, Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 5, Folder 42)
  - Correspondence from Terry Lion, 1990-09-10; 60 Linear Feet (Box 5, Folder 43)
  - Decomposition into Intrinsic & Time Value, Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 5, Folder 44)
  - Personal Contacts, 1989-1990; 60 Linear Feet (Box 5, Folder 45)
  - IMCC & Avnet Prospectus, 1987-1988; 60 Linear Feet (Box 5, Folder 46)
  - North Holland Publishing Instructions, 1990; 60 Linear Feet (Box 5, Folder 47)
  - Revuz & Ver, Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 5, Folder 48)
  - The Valuation of Options for Alternative Stochastic Processes, Cox & Ross, 1976; 60 Linear Feet (Box 5, Folder 49)
  - A Theory of the Term Structure of Interest Rates; Cox, Ingersoll, Ross, 1983-1985; 60 Linear Feet (Box 5, Folder 50)
  - Le Gall, J.F.; Spatial Branching Processes, Random Snakes & PDE's, Undated (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Buhlman's Notes on CIR, Undated (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Stock Price as Difference of 2 Bessel Squared with Same Dimension, Undated (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Liuren's Tables, Undated (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Email - Liuren Wu, 1999-12 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Carr & Wu; Market Fear of Contagion, Diversification, and Option Pricing, 2000-02 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Carr & Wu, A Consistent Framework for Derivative Pricing, 1999-10-2000-01 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Doodling with Liuren, Undated (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Results for BDW (Bonds with Detachable Warrants)/Warrants Paper, Undated (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - CIR Bond Pricing, Undated (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Option on the Sum, 2000-08-22-2000-08-23 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Bessel Squared Process & Basket Options, 2000-07-19 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Basket Options via Displaced Diffusion, 1999-04 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Basket Options for Stochastic Area, 2000-07-09-2000-07-19 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - A Basket of Basket Option Models, 2000-07-11 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Basket Options for Cox-Ross Model, Undated (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Vol's Approach to Reaction Diffusion/Quadratic Potential, 1999-10-23-1999-10-31 (Box 6, Folder 17)
- Series VI: Closed Form Barrier Option Valuation & Closed Form Option Volume with Smiles, 1994-2005
  - Closed Form Barrier Option Valuation with Smiles, Peter Carr, 2002-08-07-2003-03-26 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Solvable Potentials, 2002-04-23 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Manuscripts, 1999-04-11-2002-02-17 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Closed Form Barrier Option Valuation with Smiles, 1999-10-2002-02 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Detemple, J.; American Options: Symmetry Properties, 1999-03-02 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Roberts & Shortland, Pricing Barrier Options with Time Dependent Coefficients, Cambridge University Press, 1994 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Branoff, Paul, Undated (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Rogers, C.; The Joint Law of the Maximum and Terminal Value of a Martingale, University of Bath, Undated (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - Arcsinhnomal Model Valuation of Barrier Options, 1999-04-10 (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - Depressed Cubic in Sinh Model Valuation of Barrier Options, 1999-04-10 (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - Andreasen, J.; Behind the Mirror, Risk, 2001-11 (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - Hedging Complex Barrier Options, 1997-10-25 (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - Enhanced Delta Hedging of Barrier Options, 2001-11-17 (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - Parity Preserving PDE, 2001-11-07-2001-11-10 (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - Dobric Paper, 2001-07-31 (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - FPT Payer for Vol a Function of Price Alone, 1998-03-14-2000-10-17 (Box 6, Folder 33)
  - FPT PDF's via Infinite Discontinuity of Delta^(1) at Bday, 2001-07-14 (Box 6, Folder 34)
  - Barrier Option Pricing Using Odd Functions of Process with Known PDF, 2001-03-31 (Box 6, Folder 35)
  - Barrier Option Pricing with Stochastic Vol, 2000-02-10 (Box 6, Folder 36)
  - Recovering Local Vol from Option Prices, 1999-04-06 (Box 6, Folder 37)
  - Barrier Options for Symmetric Mg Jump Processes, 2000-01-26-2000-02-04 (Box 6, Folder 38)
  - Barrier Options via Stationary Solutions, 1999-01-19-1999-03-09 (Box 6, Folder 39)
  - Static Hedging in Arcsinhnomal Model, 1999-03-26-1999-05-02 (Box 6, Folder 40)
  - Int'g Calculations with SBM, Undated (Box 6, Folder 41)
  - Static Hedging of Barrier Options for Constant Ahs Vol (Ahs at Origin), 1999-04-11 (Box 6, Folder 42)
  - Lerche, Hans; Boundary Crossing of Brownian Motion, Springer, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 43)
  - Barrier Options under Martingale Vol, 1999-01-11-1999-01-18 (Box 6, Folder 44)
  - FPT for Time & Space Dependent Vol, 1999-02-25 (Box 6, Folder 45)
  - Time Dependent Bday for SBM, 1999-02-27 (Box 6, Folder 46)
  - SBM and PDE Notes, 2001-02-20-2002-02-22 (Box 6, Folder 47)
  - Nonlinear PDE for Volatility, 2005-10-31 (Box 6, Folder 48)
  - Dominici, Nested: Derivatives: A Simple Method for Computing Series Expansions of Inverse Functions, Journal Not Given, 2005-01-04 (Box 6, Folder 49)
  - Mania & Tevzadze, Semimartingale Functions of a Class of Diffusion Processes, Vol 4s #2, TPA, 2001 (Box 6, Folder 50)
  - General Binomial Theorem, 2001-11-20-2001-11-22 (Box 6, Folder 51)
  - Closed Form Rewrite, 2001-01-17-2001-11-24 (Box 6, Folder 52)
  - Manuscript, 1999-12-05 (Box 6, Folder 53)
  - Models to Try, 2001-11-20 (Box 6, Folder 54)
  - Intuition on Auth. Indep., 2000-06-22 (Box 6, Folder 55)
  - Appendix on Uniqueness, 1999-03-23-1999-05-26 (Box 6, Folder 56)
  - Conditions on Phi for Realistic Lognormal Vol, 1998-09-22-1999-02-14 (Box 6, Folder 57)
  - Comments on "Closed Form Option Valuation", 1999-09-01-1999-10-22 (Box 6, Folder 58)
  - Closed Form Option Valuations with Smiles, 1998-03-08-1999-04-05 (Box 6, Folder 59)
  - Delta - Closed Form Option Valuation with Smiles, 1999-01-08-1999-01-10 (Box 6, Folder 60)
  - Depressed Cubic, 1998-12-06-1999-03-20 (Box 6, Folder 61)
  - Depressed Cubic in Sinh, Undated (Box 6, Folder 62)
  - Deterministic Time Change, 1999-01-16 (Box 6, Folder 63)
  - Failed Models for Stock Price, 1998-12-30-1999-02-13 (Box 6, Folder 64)
  - FPT for Ratio of Stock Price to Probability Density, 1998-09-08 (Box 6, Folder 65)
  - Fourier Inversion to Get g, 1998-09-26-1998-10-01 (Box 6, Folder 66)
  - Functions of Bessel Processes, Undated (Box 6, Folder 67)
  - Hyperbolic Functions, Undated (Box 6, Folder 68)
  - Implications of SFC (Stock Flow Consistent) & Linearity, 1998-12-28 (Box 6, Folder 69)
  - Integrals of Derivative Securities, 1993-02-1999-01-11 (Box 6, Folder 70)
  - Inversing s Function, 1999-02-07 (Box 6, Folder 71)
  - Journal Submissions, 1999-06-01-2000-06-06 (Box 6, Folder 72)
  - Mapping Matrix to s(x,c), 1998-09-18-1998-09-21 (Box 6, Folder 73)
  - Multiplying Original Payoff by Exponential, 1999-01-05 (Box 6, Folder 74)
  - Numerical Evaluation, 1999-01-11 (Box 6, Folder 75)
  - PDE for Variance, Undated (Box 6, Folder 76)
  - PDF of Stock Price, 1999-02-15 (Box 6, Folder 77)
  - Sinh at Drifting BM, 1998-08-29 (Box 6, Folder 78)
  - Quadratic Payoff, Undated (Box 6, Folder 79)
  - Sinh & [Equation], 1998-07-30-1998-08-13 (Box 6, Folder 80)
  - Special Functions, 1999-02-07-1999-02-14 (Box 6, Folder 81)
  - Stock Payoff is an Odd Function, 1999-02-06-1999-02-07 (Box 6, Folder 82)
  - Stock Price as Cube of Sinh, 1998-12-30-1999-04-03 (Box 6, Folder 83)
  - Stock Price as Linear Combination of Sinhs, 1999-02-07 (Box 6, Folder 84)
  - Stock Propl. to Absorbing BM, 1998-01-03-1999-01-03 (Box 6, Folder 85)
  - Stock Payoff is Non-Monotonic Function of SBM, Undated (Box 6, Folder 86)
  - Thaleia Zariphopoulou, 1999-05-11 (Box 6, Folder 87)
  - Taylor Series, 1998-01-04 (Box 6, Folder 88)
  - Transforming Solutions to the Heat Equation, 1999-10-19 (Box 6, Folder 89)
  - 2 Boundaries, 1998-09-10 (Box 6, Folder 90)
  - Utility Based Approach, Undated (Box 6, Folder 91)
  - On the Valuation of Corporate Liabilities Using Option Prices, 1998-09-15-1998-09-19 (Box 6, Folder 92)
- Series VII: Closed Form Option Valuation Extensions, 1980-2002
  - ABM as Driver, 1999-11; 60 Linear Feet (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Manuscripts - Volatility Surface, 1998; 60 Linear Feet (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Arbitrary Stochastic Time Change, Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - CM Stock Payoffs, 1998; 60 Linear Feet (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Driver is BM with Drift, Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - From Inverse Distribution Function to Option Prices, 1999; 60 Linear Feet (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Elliptic Integrals, 1999-02; 60 Linear Feet (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Explanation Why for Stochastic Pricing Functions (in Time), 1999-02; 60 Linear Feet (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Fourier Transforms, 1998; 60 Linear Feet (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Generating Explicity Invertible Payoffs by Composing Explicitly Invertible Operators, 1999; 60 Linear Feet (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Depressed Cubic in Depressed Cubic, Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Depressed Cubic in Depressed Cubic in Sinh, 1999-04-06; 60 Linear Feet (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Unlabeled Formula and Notes, Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - A Theory of the Volatility Surface, 1998; 60 Linear Feet (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Approximating Basket Options, Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Hermite Polynomials, 1998-2002; 60 Linear Feet (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Integration in Finite Terms, 1999; 60 Linear Feet (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Measurement Units, 1999-02-14; 60 Linear Feet (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Oven Invertible Stock Pricing Functions, 1999-04-18; 60 Linear Feet (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Option Pricing is a Cinch, 1999-02; 60 Linear Feet (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Piecewise Globally Specification, 1999-02-09; 60 Linear Feet (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Positive Processes, 2000-01-31; 60 Linear Feet (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Quartic in Exp'l Quadratics, 1998-12-12; 60 Linear Feet (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Quintic in SBM, 2002-01; 60 Linear Feet (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Scale & Time Changes when Drift is Function of Price & Time, 1999-03; 60 Linear Feet (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Similarity Solution for Sigma or c, 1998-1999; 60 Linear Feet (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - Spun of G^1, Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - Spine Specification of Stock Pricing Function, 1998-12-28; 60 Linear Feet (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - Stock Price as Positive Linear Combination of Exponents, 1998-1999; 60 Linear Feet (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - Stock as Wtd Average of GBMs, 1998-1999; 60 Linear Feet (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - Stochastic Time Change & GT, 1999-03-15; 60 Linear Feet (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - Stock Payoff is Exp'l Quintatic less Constant, 1999-02-21; 60 Linear Feet (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - Stock is Constant & Proper Rational Function, 1999-02-22; 60 Linear Feet (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - Stock Process Driven by a Pair of SBMs, 1999; 60 Linear Feet (Box 7, Folder 34)
  - Stock Payoff is (1+ z/m)^m, z normal in real, 1999-02; 60 Linear Feet (Box 7, Folder 35)
  - Time Inversion, 1999-06-18; 60 Linear Feet (Box 7, Folder 36)
  - Time Value via Quintative, 1999-02-11; 60 Linear Feet (Box 7, Folder 37)
  - Stock Price is Odd Function of Process with Symmetric PDF, 2000-01; 60 Linear Feet (Box 7, Folder 38)
  - Stock Price is Even Function of Reflecting BM, 1999-03-14; 60 Linear Feet (Box 7, Folder 39)
  - Stock is Quartic of Ce^aw Divided by a Power less than or equal to 4, 1999-02; 60 Linear Feet (Box 7, Folder 40)
  - Modelling Payoff of Brownian Pricing Function, 1998-1999; 60 Linear Feet (Box 7, Folder 41)
  - Uchiyama, K.; Brownian First Exist from & Sojourn over One Sided Moving Boundary and Application, 1980; 60 Linear Feet (Box 7, Folder 42)
  - Time Homogenous Vol Functions, 1999-03-06; 60 Linear Feet (Box 7, Folder 43)
  - Time Region Specification, 1998; 60 Linear Feet (Box 7, Folder 44)
- Series VIII: Compound Exchange Options (CEO), 1986-1994
  - A Sequential Exchange Option, 1994; 60 Linear Feet (Box 7, Folder 45)
  - The Valuation of Sequential Exchange Opportunities Originals (1), 1986-1988; 60 Linear Feet (Box 7, Folder 46)
  - The Valuation of Sequential Exchange Opportunities Originals (2), 1987; 60 Linear Feet (Box 7, Folder 47)
  - The Valuation of Sequential Exchange Opportunities Copies, 1988; 60 Linear Feet (Box 7, Folder 48)
  - Latest Session - CEO, 1988-01; 60 Linear Feet (Box 7, Folder 49)
  - Journal of Finance Correspondence - CEO, 1987-1988; 60 Linear Feet (Box 7, Folder 50)
  - CEO Revisions and Comments (1), 1986-1987; 60 Linear Feet (Box 7, Folder 51)
  - CEO Revisions and Comments (2), 1986; 60 Linear Feet (Box 7, Folder 52)
  - Compound Exchange Options Notes, Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 7, Folder 53)
- Series IX: Conservative Fields & Hedging, 2001-2004
  - Static Hedging & Exotic Options Notes, 2004-06-16; 60 Linear Feet (Box 7, Folder 54)
  - Semi-Static Hedging & Conservative Fields, 2002; 60 Linear Feet (Box 7, Folder 55)
  - Markov Assn. & Static Hedging, 2002-11-14; 60 Linear Feet (Box 7, Folder 56)
  - Vertical Static Hedge and Stochastic Vol., 2002; 60 Linear Feet (Box 7, Folder 57)
  - FPT Payer, 2002-11-23; 60 Linear Feet (Box 7, Folder 58)
  - Stochastic Representation of Results, 2002-11-24; 60 Linear Feet (Box 7, Folder 59)
  - Vertical Static Hedge, 2002-11-24; 60 Linear Feet (Box 7, Folder 60)
  - Dim I Analysis of PCR, 2002-04-25; 60 Linear Feet (Box 7, Folder 61)
  - Random Time/SV, 2002-07-03; 60 Linear Feet (Box 7, Folder 62)
  - Signing Call Delta & Gamma For Markov Semi-Martingales, 2001-2002; 60 Linear Feet (Box 7, Folder 63)
  - Higher Order Term Representations in Backward PIDE, 2002; 60 Linear Feet (Box 7, Folder 64)
  - PCR Using Delta Functions & Gamma as Transition PDF, 2002; 60 Linear Feet (Box 7, Folder 65)
  - Interpreting BCP(I)DE as a FpP(I)DE, 2002; 60 Linear Feet (Box 7, Folder 66)
  - Semi-Static Hedging & Conservative Fields - Old Manuscripts, 2002; 60 Linear Feet (Box 7, Folder 67)
- Series X: Convertible Bonds, 1996-2003
  - Integration of PDE in Finite-Difference Scheme; Mane, S.R., 2003-04-20; 60 Linear Feet (Box 7, Folder 68)
  - Mane, S.R.; Discrete Dividends in a Finite-Difference Scheme, 2003-03-22; 60 Linear Feet (Box 7, Folder 69)
  - Kynex, 2000-2003; 60 Linear Feet (Box 7, Folder 70)
  - Contingent Convertibles, 2001; 60 Linear Feet (Box 7, Folder 71)
  - CVS, Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 7, Folder 72)
  - DECS, Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 7, Folder 73)
  - MBRM (Mamdoh Barakat Risk Management), Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 7, Folder 74)
  - OAS, Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 7, Folder 75)
  - Soft Call, 2001; 60 Linear Feet (Box 7, Folder 76)
  - Testing Against MBRM, 2001-04; 60 Linear Feet (Box 7, Folder 77)
  - Van Mtgs, 2001-03-12; 60 Linear Feet (Box 7, Folder 78)
  - CB Proposal - Notes, 1997-2001; 60 Linear Feet (Box 7, Folder 79)
  - CBIFAC, 2001; 60 Linear Feet (Box 7, Folder 80)
  - BofA, Equity Derivative Applications for Convertible Bond Investors, 2001-03; 60 Linear Feet (Box 7, Folder 81)
  - Convertible Bonds Bibliography, Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 7, Folder 82)
  - Convertible Bond Decomposition into Bond Plus Amer. Call, 2001-11-30; 60 Linear Feet (Box 7, Folder 83)
  - Email on CBs at MS, 1998-07-27; 60 Linear Feet (Box 7, Folder 84)
  - Convertible Bonds MS, 1996-2001; 60 Linear Feet (Box 7, Folder 85)
  - Tru-Calc, 2000-07-17; 60 Linear Feet (Box 7, Folder 86)
  - Finite-Difference Methods for Two-Factor Models Reprint, 2001; 60 Linear Feet (Box 7, Folder 87)
  - Borrow Costs for Convert., Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 7, Folder 88)
  - CB Model Testing, 2001; 60 Linear Feet (Box 7, Folder 89)
- Series XI: Convolution Transform, 1988-2004
  - Pestana & Mendonça, Higher-Order Monotone Functions and Probability Theory, Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 7, Folder 90)
  - Intuition on Convolution Equations, 2004; 60 Linear Feet (Box 7, Folder 91)
  - PDEs for Jump Diffusions, 2000-2004; 60 Linear Feet (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Csordas & Varga, Integral Transforms and the Laguerre-Polya Class, 1989; 60 Linear Feet (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Convolution Transform Notes, Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Cardon, D.A.; Convolution Operators and Zeros of Entire Functions, 2001-10-17; 60 Linear Feet (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Carr & Mayo, On the Numerical Evaluation of Option Prices in Jump Diffusion Processes, Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Madan, D.B.; Approximating Levy Processes, 2004-12-16; 60 Linear Feet (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Anita Mayo, Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Using Convolution Transforms to Create Enhanced Delta Hedge, Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Baumer, B.; On the Inversion of the Convolution and Laplace Transform, Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Zayed & Haimo, Inversion of an Integral Transform Related to a General Form of Heat Equation, 1988; 60 Linear Feet (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Zayed & Haimo, Inversion of Integral Transforms Associated with a Class of Perturbed Heat Equations, 1992; 60 Linear Feet (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Dulilip's Result for Local Levy Processes, Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - The Convolution Transform, Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Anita Mayo Notes, Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Solving for Static Hedges Using Convolution Transforms, 2004-07-16 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Dewy Integral in PIDE Implicitly Using Convolution Transforms, Undated (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Briani, La Chioma & Natalini; Convergence of Numerical Schemes for Viscosity Solutions to Integro-Differential Degenerate Parabolic Problems Arising in Financial Theory, Undated (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Carr, Geman, Madan & Yor; From Local Volatility to Local Levy Models, 2004-02 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Carr & Mayo, On the Numerical Evaluation of Option Prices in Jump Diffusion Processes, Undated (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Kou & Wang, First Passage Times of a Jump Diffusion Process, Advances in Applied Probability, 2003 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Kou, S.; A Jump-Diffusion Model for Option Pricing, 2002 (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Kou & Wang, Option Pricing Under a Double Exponential Jump Diffusion Model, Columbia, 2001 (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Mayo, Anita; Notes on Reducing the Solution of PIDEs in Exponential Jump Diffusion Models to the Solution of ODEs, Undated (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - Papapantoleon & Senge, Option Pricing in a Jump Diffusion Model with Double Exponential Jumps, 2002-06-06 (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - Pensky & Vidakovic, Adaptive Wavelet Estimator for Nonparametric Density Deconvolution, Annals of Statistics, 1999 (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - Pinkus, A.; Spectral Properties of Totally Positive Kernels and Matrices, 1995 (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - Schoenberg, I.; On Totally Positive Functions, Laplace Integrals and Entire Functions of the Laguerre-Polya-Schur Type; Mathematics 1947, Undated (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - Zayed, Ch. 17: The Convolution Transform, Undated (Box 8, Frame 28)
- Series XII: Covariance Contracting, 1989-1999
  - Cov Between Futured Fixed Inc., 1999-07-06; 60 Linear Feet (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - BIV BM Approximation, 1989-1997; 60 Linear Feet (Box 8, Folder 30)
  - Quantics for Ajay, 1998-03-06; 60 Linear Feet (Box 8, Folder 31)
  - Amin, K.I.; JFQA; On the Computation of Continuous Time Option Prices Using Discrete Approximations, 1991-12; 60 Linear Feet (Box 8, Folder 32)
  - Currency Protected Securities (CPS), 1998; 60 Linear Feet (Box 8, Folder 33)
  - Implied Covariance Quantics, 1989-1998; 60 Linear Feet (Box 8, Folder 34)
  - Quantics, 1997-1998; 60 Linear Feet (Box 8, Folder 35)
  - Dimensioning in Cov Swap, Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 8, Folder 36)
  - T-Bill Returns & Futures, 1999-07; 60 Linear Feet (Box 8, Folder 37)
  - Risk Submission, 1998-1999; 60 Linear Feet (Box 8, Folder 38)
  - Burns, Engle & Mezrich; Correlations and Volatilities of Asynchronous Data, 1998; 60 Linear Feet (Box 8, Folder 39)
  - Engle & Mezrich, Garch for Groups, 1996-08; 60 Linear Feet (Box 8, Folder 40)
  - Currency Covariance Contracting, 1998; 60 Linear Feet (Box 8, Folder 41)
  - Wang, C.H.; The Geocultural, Economic, and Financial Reasons for International Equity Market, 1998-11-09; 60 Linear Feet (Box 8, Folder 42)
  - Idea Using Legendre Process, Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 8, Folder 43)
  - Gesser, V.; Correlation Risk, Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 8, Folder 44)
  - Beta Contracts, Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 8, Folder 45)
  - Covariance Contracting, 1997-1998; 60 Linear Feet (Box 8, Folder 46)
  - Carr & Corso, Commodity Covariance Contracting, 1998-01-01; 60 Linear Feet (Box 8, Folder 47)
  - Correlation Contract, Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 8, Folder 48)
- Series XIII: Constant Proportion Portfolio Insurance (CPPI), 1989-2006
  - CPPI w/ Alexey Polishchuk Publication, 2005-2006; 60 Linear Feet (Box 8, Folder 49)
  - Power Chain shown as Numerative & Being Consistent with Stress through Drift, 2005-02; 60 Linear Feet (Box 8, Folder 50)
  - Crash Showed Danger of Insured Assets, 1997-10-13; 60 Linear Feet (Box 8, Folder 51)
  - Renoux, Yann, 2006-02; 60 Linear Feet (Box 8, Folder 52)
  - CPPI with Trading at Hitting Times, 2006-02; 60 Linear Feet (Box 8, Folder 53)
  - Chris Cummins, Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 8, Folder 54)
  - Discrete Hedging for CPPI, Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 8, Folder 55)
  - CPPI Cush.dS, 2006-06-28; 60 Linear Feet (Box 8, Folder 56)
  - Alternative CPPI Strategies, Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 8, Folder 57)
  - Options in CPPI, 2005; 60 Linear Feet (Box 8, Folder 58)
  - Funds of Hedge Funds & Structured Products, 2006-09-02; 60 Linear Feet (Box 8, Folder 59)
  - CPPI, 2005-2006; 60 Linear Feet (Box 8, Folder 60)
  - 2D CPPI, 2006-02-28; 60 Linear Feet (Box 8, Folder 61)
  - Portfolio Insurance History (1), 1989-2006; 60 Linear Feet (Box 8, Folder 62)
  - Portfolio Insurance History (2), 2001-2006; 60 Linear Feet (Box 8, Folder 63)
  - Zhu, Ernest; European Claims on CPPI, 2006-10-19; 60 Linear Feet (Box 8, Folder 64)
  - Zhu, E.; European Options in CPPI, 2005-11-29; 60 Linear Feet (Box 8, Folder 65)
- Series XIV: D3 Non BS Path Dependent, 1990-2004
  - Applications of Time Reversal to Asset Pricing Theory, 2001-04-07 (Box 8, Folder 66)
  - Applications of TR & PCR, 2001-07-09-2001-08-07 (Box 8, Folder 67)